Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. 16mm microfilm Accounting Department records, 1942-1954 RL.11717
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Production Billing, 1942-1953; 3
  - Production billing carbons, New York, 1946 (Reel 324)
    Penick & Ford; Pennsylvania Central Air Lines; Pepsodent; Pharma-Craft; Planters Nut and Chocolate; Putnam Trust of Greenwich; RCA
  - Production billing carbons, New York, 1946 (Reel 325)
    RCA; Reader's Digest international edition; Reynolds Metals; Rheem; Rystan; Scott Paper; Scranton Lace; Sharp & Dohme; Shell Oil (Eastern territory, West Coast)
  - Production billing carbons, New York, 1947 (Reel 340)
    Kodak; Equitable Life Association Society; Fanny Farmer Candy Shops; Ford
  - Production billing carbons, New York, 1947 (Reel 344)
    Ford; General Cigar
  - Production billing carbons, New York, 1947 (Reel 345)
    Gillette; Arthur Guinness; Associated Hospital Services; Horlick's; Institute of Life Insurance; Irving Trust; Johns-Manville; Kroy Wool Processors; Lamont-Corliss; Lever (Lux Flakes, Lux Toilet Soap, Vimms); Massachusetts Hospital Service; Mentholatum
  - Production billing carbons, New York, 1947 (Reel 346)
    Mentholatum; Nashua Manufacturing; National Broadcasting; National Fisheries; National Peanut Council; New York Yankees; Omega Watch; Owens-Illinois Glass; Oxford University Press; Pan Am; Penick & Ford; Pharma-Craft; RCA
  - Production billing carbons, New York, 1947 (Reel 347)
    RCA; Reader's Digest international edition; Reynolds Metals
  - Production billing carbons, New York, 1947 (Reel 348)
    Reynolds Metals; Rystan; Sarfert Hosiery Mills; Scott Paper; Scranton Lace; Sharp & Dohme; Shell Oil (East Coast, West Coast); E.R. Squibb & Sons; Standard Brands; Sundries; Textron; Tupman Motors; United Cut Flowers; U.S. Brewers Foundation
  - Production billing carbons, New York, 1947 (Reel 349)
    U.S. Brewers Foundation; U.S. Lines; U.S. Playing Card; Ward Baking; Northam Warren; Western Union; J.B. Williams; Whizzer Motor; W.F. Young; Webb Young Trader; N.Y. financial
  - Production billing carbons, New York, 1948 (Reel 391)
    P. Ballantine; Brillo; Buxton; Carter's Ink; Deglin-Wood; Fanny Farmer Candy Shops; General Cigars
  - Production billing carbons, New York, 1948 (Reel 392)
    Gillette; Arthur Guinness; Horlick's; American Hospital Association; Institute of Life Insurance; Irving Trust; Johns-Manville; Kellogg; Kroy Wool Processors; Lamont Corliss; Lever Brothers; Mentholatum; Nashua Mills; petty cash vouchers
  - Production billing carbons, New York, 1948 (Reel 393)
    National Broadcasting; National Fisheries Institute; National Peanut Council; New Holland Machine; Omega Watch; Oneida; Owens-Illinois Glass; Glass Container Manufacturing Institute; Oxford University Press; Pan Am; Penick & Ford; Pharma-Craft
  - Production billing carbons, New York, 1948 (Reel 394)
    RCA petty cash vouchers; Reader's Digest international edition; Rystan; Sarfert Hosiery Mills; Scott Paper; Scranton Lace
  - Production billing carbons, New York, 1948 (Reel 395)
    Shell Oil; E.R. Squibb; Standard Brands; Textron; Thompson-toledo Vitameter; U.S. Brewers Foundation; U.S. Lines; U.S. Playing Card; Ward Baking; Western Union; Whizzer Motor; J.B. Williams; W.F. Young; Webb Young Trader; New York sundries
  - Production billing carbons, New York, 1948 (Reel 396)
    New York sundries; New York financial
  - Production billing carbons, New York, 1949 (Reel 433)
    P. Ballantine; Brillo; British Export Trade Association; Buxton; Caterpillar Tractor; Carter's Ink; Church & Dwight; Christais Prado Ltd (Sao Paulo Brazil); Devoe & Raynolds; Kodak; petty cash vouchers; Fanny Farmer Candy Shops; Farrell Lines; General Cigar; Gillette; Institute of Life Insurance
  - Production billing carbons, New York, 1949-1950 (Reel 434)
    Irving Trust; John Irving Shoe; Johns-Manville; Kroy Wool Processors; Lamont Corliss; Lever Brothers; Mentholatum; Metropolitan Motor Coaches; Michigan Hospital Service; Nashua Mills; National Broadcasting; National Fisheries Institute; New Holland Machine; petty cash vouchers
  - Production billing carbons, New York, 1949-1950 (Reel 435)
    Omega Watch; Oneida; Owens-Illinois Glass; petty cash vouchers; Oxford University Press; Pan Am; Penick & Ford; Pharma-Craft; Purolator Products
  - Production billing carbons, New York, 1949-1950 (Reel 436)
    Purolator Products; RCA; petty cash vouchers; Reader's Digest; Rystan; Scranton Lace; Shell Oil
  - Production billing carbons, New York, 1949-1950 (Reel 437)
    Shell Oil; petty cash vouchers; E.R. Squibb; Reader's Digest; New York sundries; Standard Brands; Textron; Thompson Products; U.S. Brewers Foundation; U.S. Lines; U.S. Playing Card
  - Production billing carbons, New York, 1949-1950 (Reel 438)
    Ward Baking; Western Union; Whizzer Motor; petty cash vouchers; J.B. Williams; W.F. Young; Webb Young Trader; New York sundries; New York financial; petty cash vouchers
  - Production billing carbons, New York, 1951 (Reel 772)
    Columbia Mills; Devoe & Raynolds; Kodak; Farrell Lines; Florida Citrus Commission; General Cigar; Institute of Life Insurance
  - Production billing carbons, New York, 1951 (Reel 773)
    Institute of Life Insurance; Irving Trust; Kroy Wool Processors; Lever; Johns-Manville; Massachusetts Mutual; Mentholatum; Michigan Hospital Service; NBC; New Holland Machine; Luscon Laboratories; Glasco Products; National Office Management Association; Office Equipment Manufacturers Institute; Owens Illinois Glass
  - Production billing carbons, New York, 1951 (Reel 774)
    Owens-Illinois Glass; Oneida; Oxford University Press; Pacific Mills; Pan Am; Penick & Ford; Pepsodent; Pharma-Craft; Pond's
  - Production billing carbons, New York, 1951 (Reel 775)
    Pond's; Purolator; RCA Victor Division
  - Production billing carbons, New York, 1951 (Reel 776)
    RCA Victor Division; Reader's Digest; Rystan; Scott Paper; Scranton Lace; Shell Oil; Seth Thomas; Squibb; Staze
  - Production billing carbons, New York, 1951 (Reel 777)
    Standard Brands; U.S. Playing Card; U.S. Lines; U.S. Brewers Foundation; Truck Renters of New York; Ward Baking; J.B. Williams; W.F. Young; Advertising Council
  - Production billing carbons, New York, 1952 (Reel 889)
    Burroughs; Carreras Ltd.; Carter's Ink; Carter Products; Caterpillar; Champion Spark Plug; Church & Dwight
  - Production billing carbons, New York, 1952 (Reel 890)
    Church & Dwight; Columbia Mills; Devoe & Raynolds; Kodak; Empire City Savings Bank; Fanny Farmer; Farrell Lines; Florida Citrus Commission; Happy Productions; Institute of Life Insurance; Irving Trust
  - Production billing carbons, New York, 1952 (Reel 891)
    Irving Trust; Indian Jute Mills; Jerclaydon; Johns-Manville; Lever; Massachusetts Mutual Life Insurance; Mentholatum; Michigan Hospital Service; NBC; National Fisheries Institute; New Holland Machine; Oneida; Owens-Illinois Glass
  - Production billing carbons, New York, 1952 (Reel 892)
    Owens-Illinois Glass; Pan Am; Penick & Ford; Pepsodent-Chlorodent (Rayve); Pharma-Craft; Pond's; Purolator; Putnam Trust; RCA
  - Production billing carbons, New York, 1952 (Reel 893)
    RCA; Reader's Digest international edition; Scott Paper; Shell Oil
  - Production billing carbons, New York, 1952 (Reel 894)
    Shell Oil; Alexander Smith; Squibb; Stand Corp.; Standard Brands; Staze; Seth Thomas; U.S. Brewers Foundation; U.S. Lines; U.S. Playing Card; U.S. Treasury (Savings Bonds); Ward Baking; J.B. Williams; W.F. Young
  - Production billing carbons, New York, 1952 (Reel 895)
    New York sundries
  - Production billing carbons, New York, 1953 (Reel 916)
    Burroughs; Carter Products; Champion Spark Plug; Church & Dwight; Columbia Mills; Delson Candy; Devoe & Raynolds; Kodak; Empire City Savings Bank; Fanny Farmer; Farrell Lines; Florida Citrus; Indian Jute Mills; Institute of Life Insurance; Irving Trust; Jercladon
  - Production billing carbons, New York, 1953 (Reel 917)
    Johns-Manville; Lever; Massachusetts Mutual Life Insurance; Mentholatum; Michigan Hospital Insurance; Mosler Safe; NBC; National Fisheries; New Holland Machine; Office Equipment Manufacturers Institute; Oneida; Owens-Illinois Glass
  - Production billing carbons, New York, 1953 (Reel 918)
    Owens-Illinois Glass; Pacific Mills; Pan Am; Penick & Ford; Pepsodent-Chlorodent (Rayve); Pharma-Craft; Pond's; Purolator; RCA
  - Production billing carbons, New York, 1953 (Reel 919)
    RCA; Reader's Digest; Scott Paper; Shell Oil
  - Production billing carbons, New York, 1953 (Reel 920)
    Shell Oil; Alexander Smith; Squibb; Stand Corp.; Standard Brands; Staze; Seth Thomas; U.S. Brewers Foundation; U.S. Lines; U.S. Marine Corps; U.S. Playing Card; U.S. Treasury (Savings Bonds); Upholstery Leather Group; Ward Baking
  - Production billing carbons, New York and California, 1944 (Reel 296)
    New York: alphabetical from Reynolds Metals; California starting with Ayde Medical Products
  - Production billing carbons, New York and Chicago, 1944-1945 (Reel 302)
    New York: sundries; Chicago: Libby McNeil & Libby
  - Production billing carbons, New York and Chicago, 1945-1946 (Reel 326)
    Shell Oil (West Coast); Shell Chemical; Chicago: Appliance Corporation of America; Borg-Warner; Bowman Dairy; Chicago Tribune; H.C. Cole Milling; Elgin National Watch; Ford
  - Production billing carbons, New York and Chicago, 1949-1950 (Reel 439)
    New York financial; Chicago: American Red Cross; Arnold Schwinn; Borg-Warner; Bowman Dairy; E.J. Brach; Chicago Heart Association; Crown Jewel Ware; Elgin Natonal Watch; Illinois Bronze Powder; Illinois Power; Indiana Bell Telephone; petty cash vouchers; International Minerals and Chemical; Kistler Radar Sandwich; Kraft
  - Production billing carbons, New York and San Francisco, 1948 (Reel 397)
    New York financial--petty cash vouchers; San Francisco: Bateman-Eichler; F.W. Boltz; Douglas Aircraft; Garrett; Glass Container Manufacturing of California; Holly Sugar; Home Builders Council of California; Judy Crib Sheet Co.; Kraft (See also Chicago office); Langendorf United Bakeries; Lawrence Warehouse; Mabs of Hollywood; Magna Engineering; Leo J. Meyberg; Mayflower Doughnut; McClatchy Broadcasting; NBC
  - Production billing carbons, New York, Detroit, Chicago, 1947 (Reel 350)
    N.Y. financial; Detroit sundry, painted bulletins; Chicago: Appliance Corporation of America; Borg-Warner; Bowman Dairy; H.C. Cole Milling; Elgin Watch; Hixson Products; Illinois Power; Kellogg; Kent Products; Kraft; Libby McNeil & Libby
  - Production billing carbons, New York, West Coast and Chicago, 1953 (Reel 921)
    Ward Baking; J.B. Williams; W.F. Young; New York sundries; West Coast offices; Chicago: American Medical Association; American Trucking Association; Blue Cross; Borg-Warner
  - Production billing carbons, San Francisco, 1946 (Reel 385)
    Downtown financial; Apparel; Bateman Eichler; Boyle-Midway; Calavo Growers of California; California Desert Grapefruit; California Lima Beans; J.E. Coberly; Douglas Aircraft; Garrett; E. Green; E.P. Halliburton; Hollywood Magazine; J.P. Hardemann; Hotel Last Frontier; Kraft; Los Angeles Times; Los Vegas Chamber of Commerce; Mabs of Hollywood; McClatchy Newspapers; Mutual Orange District; Northrop Aircraft; Northrop Gaines; Puget Sound; Rheem; Safeway Stores
  - Production billing carbons, San Francisco, 1948 (Reel 398)
    Pan Am; Panama Pacific Line; Puget Sound Navigation; Parlyn Ltd.; RCA Victor Division; Safeway Stores; Sunset Magazine; Southern California Citrus Foods; Seven-Up; Sellmar Products; Storkline Furniture; sundries; Swift
  - Production billing carbons, San Francisco and Chicago, 1948 (Reel 399)
    San Francisco: Times Mirror; United Artists; Veloz & Yolander; Washington State Apple Advisory Commission; Washburn-Wilson Seed Co.; Wine Advisory Board; Chicago: Arnold Schwinn; Borg-Warner; Bowman Dairy petty cash vouchers; Crown Jewel Ware; Elgin National Watch; Famous Flours; Hixson Products; Illinois Power; Indiana Bell Telephone; International Minerals and Chemical; Kraft (see also San Francisco office)
  - Production billing carbons, San Francisco and New York, 1946-1948 (Reel 386)
    Safeway Stores; Spreckels; Sunset Magazine; Swift; Threlkeld; Todd Pacific Shipyards; J.T. Troll; Tupman Motors; Twentieth Century Frocks; Washington State Apples; Western Growers; Wine Advisory Board; miscellaneous; American Weekly; Anthracite Institute; Atlantis Sales; P. Ballantine
  - Production billing carbons, West Coast, 1952 (Reel 900)
    Garrett; Garrett Supply; Henderize; Halley Sugar; Kraft; Lawrence Warehouse; Los Angeles Mirror; Lucerne Milk; McClatchy Newspapers; Lee J. Meyberg; Millstream Cereal; Mutual Savings and Loan; NBC Western Network; NBC-KNBC; Old Fashion Products; Olive Advisory Board; Pan Am; Pineapple Growers Association of Hawaii; Puget Sound Navigation; Raisin Advisory Board; Real Gold Citrus; Safeway Stores; San Francisco Chronicle; Shell Chemical; Southwest Airways; Sunset Magazine; Tuna Research Foundation; Washington State Apples; Washington State Dairy Products; Washington State Ferries; Wine Advisory Board; Yellow Cab of Los Angeles
  - Talent pay cards, 1950-1951 (Reel 879)
    1950: A-Z; 1951: A-F
  - Talent pay cards, 1951-1952 (Reel 880)
    1951: F (Forrest)-Z; 1952: A-P
  - Talent pay cards, 1952 (Reel 881)
    1952: Q-Z; models; rights and independent contractors
  - Talent pay cards, 1952 (Reel 884)
    Refilmed see reel 881; Woodruff (Nancy), Wyatt (dana), Wymore (Patrice)